# **Yuri Panov**

# android developer

Born: 5-apr-83, Moscow, Russia

Education: University

Phone: +54 9 11 3214 7310
Email: panovyuria@gmail.com

Address: **Argentina, Córdoba, Casa Grande** 

Web: GitHub :: yupanov LinkedIn :: yupanov



# **Education**

#### **University:**

2002.9-2006.3 Moscow University of Ministry of Internal Affairs of Russia,

bachelors degree in Law

**Courses:** 

2020.3-2020.7 CFP 31, Buenos Aires, Java, MySQL db

2020.8-2020.12 Codo a codo, Buenos Aires, Full stack web design

2020.8-2020.12 CFP 11, Buenos Aires, Python

2021.4-2021.7 Online course Udacity, Android development with Kotlin

# Skills

### **Technologies:**

**Languages**: Kotlin, Java, JavaScript, C++ (Arduino),

Python, SQL

Android: SDK, MVVM, LiveData, DataBinding, Navigation, Glide, Room, Retrofit, RecyclerView, ViewPager2, FusedLocation etc.

#### Other:

Git, Jira

VS Code, HTML, CSS, React,

NodeJS, MongoDB

#### Languages:

I am fluent in Russian, Spanish, English and Portuguese.

#### Soft skills:

I am sociable, honest, responsible, good leader, creative, adaptive, autodidact, acting well in stress conditions, I have experience forming motivated teams around me.



### **Experience**

**2022.4-2022.11 GEOPAGOS, android developer**. Mainly I was fixing bugs, developing small features and porting legacy apps to a new codebase.

Prior to that, I worked as a graphic designer, a photographer and a refrigeration technician, I organized tango schools in Russia and Argentina.

My programmer skills are shown in the application **Resume Yuri Panov**, where I implemented the most important technologies I domain. You can see it on **yupanov.github.io** (scan QR).



my app



### **About me**

I was born in Russia and for the last 8 years I live in Argentina. I am interested in a career in IT, Android developing and the best practices in POO are my main focuses.

My passions include travelling, cycling, programming and crafting in my home workshop. I am a tango dancer and teacher.

# **Yuri Panov**

android developer

Nacido: 5-abr-83, Moscú, Rusia

Educación: Universidad

Teléfono: +54 9 11 3214 7310 Email: panovyuria@gmail.com

Dirección: Argentina, Córdoba, Casa Grande

Web: GitHub:: yupanov LinkedIn:: yupanov



# **Educación**

**Universidad:** 

2002.9-2006.3 Universidad del Ministerio del Interior (Moscú, Rusia),

bachiller, derecho

**Cursos:** 

2020.3-2020.7 CFP 31, Buenos Aires, Java, MySQL db

2020.8-2020.12 Codo a codo, Buenos Aires, Full stack diseño Web

CFP 11, Buenos Aires, Python 2020.8-2020.12

Curso online Udacity, desarrollo para Android con Kotlin 2021.4-2021.7

# **Habilidades**

**Technologías:** 

Lenguajes: Kotlin, Java, JavaScript, C++ (Arduino),

Python, SQL

Android: SDK, MVVM, LiveData, DataBinding, Navigation, Glide, Room, Retrofit, RecyclerView, ViewPager2, FusedLocation etc.

Otros: Git, Jira

VS Code, HTML, CSS, React,

NodeJS, MongoDB.

**Idiomas:** 

Yo hablo v escribo en Ruso, Español, Inglés y Portugués. **Habilidades blandas** (soft skills):

Soy sociable, honesto, responsable, buen líder, creativo, adaptivo, autodidacta, resistente al estrés, tengo experiencia en generar equipos motivados a mi alrededor.



## **Experiencia**

2022.4-2022.11 GEOPAGOS, android developer. Principalmente mi trabajo fue corregir errores y pasar aplicaciones legacy a nueva base de código.

Anteriormente trabajé como diseñador gráfico, fotógrafo, técnico de refrigeración, organicé varios proyectos tangueros en Rusia y en Argentina.

Mis habilidades como prograrmador están demostradas en la aplicación CV Yuri Panov, en la cuál implementé las tecnologías más importantes que manejo. Se puede verla en **yupanov.github.io** (escanear QR).





### Presentación

Nací en Rusia y los últimos ocho años vivo en Argentina. Estoy interesado en la carrera en IT, el desarrollo de aplicaciones para Android y mejores prácticas en POO actualmente me llaman la mayor atención.

Aparte de la programación me gusta bailar tango, viajar, andar en bicicleta y trabajar en mi taller casero.